[{"answer": "OK.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "-- you've been a very naughty boy, haven't you?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "Oh, this is getting weird.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "You know what happens to naughty boys back in Britain?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "You know what happens to naughty boys, Ricky.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Larry King never did this?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Do you feel remotely remorseful?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "You said these terrible things about these pampered prima donnas in Hollywood.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "What have I done wrong?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Let me remind you.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Well, what did I say that was so bad?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "So you just conveniently came up with that line?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "I mean, that was a tea party compared to your standup.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "What exactly?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "I want to make people laugh, and I want to do a good job, but on my terms, really.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "What is your aim at?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "With the Globes, for example.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "What, you mean officials?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "So, the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, they have no warning of what's coming?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Well, I like your confidence.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Do you really think he's hurt that I didn't like \"The Tourist\"?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "There's nothing you shouldn't joke about.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Are there any limits in comedy?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "You take the art of comedy pretty seriously.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "I don't know, Ashton Kutcher, Bruce Willis?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Bruce was there, right?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Of course he was joking.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Was he joking?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "ERVAIS: Because I've met him, and he's got a great sense of humor.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "How do you know?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Did you meet him afterwards?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "But do you care -- let me ask you --", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know if they have an addiction.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Do you care about what they may be going through in their private lives?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Also, I'm not judging them.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "If you did, would it make a difference?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "No I'm not.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "You're mocking them, aren't you?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Well, if you're a believer in God, if you're a Christian, as many tens of millions in America are --", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "What's up with that?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Yes, because you're kind of mocking them there.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What, because I'm saying I don't believe in God?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "I used to go to Sunday school all the time, I believed in -- well, you've got to realize that when you're a working class kid -- I came from a very poor, working class background.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "And what happened to change your mind then?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "I'll be rewarded now.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "What do you think will happen to you?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "People who liked me will remember me.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "But when you die, what do you think happens?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Well, not in that sense.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Are you a spiritual person?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I don't believe there's anything after.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Oh, I love it.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "When you see lists like that, you must laugh, don't you?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Anything you want to say?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "It's much more than camp.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "I mean, you're a good-looking lad, but it's pretty camp, isn't it?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "And Spandau?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "I know and that -- and that's got about three or four socks down there.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "You're proud of yourself?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "But you used to be -- when \"The Office\" came out, the great thing about you was --", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "And you still can't tell, can you?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "-- you were just chunky, chubby Ricky --", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Fourteen stone.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What was the point when you went -- how -- how heavy were you when you went that's enough?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Not then, no.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "Right, you made it; you worked hard to get it, I can't blow this; I've got to now play this game seriously?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, I didn't -- I didn't ever worry about my weight.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "About 25 pounds.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "How much have you lost?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Working out.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "And how have you done it?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "Oh, Jesus, no.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "ORGAN: Any nip and tuck?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "No, nothing.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "But I've -- I've -- I have those things on --", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Have you got vainer, do you think, since you've been a TV and film star?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Do you like being famous?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Not at all?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "Are you -- are you easy to live with?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "Would Jane say that?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "You just don't believe in God, so what's the point?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "Is that a deliberate, conscious decision?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "ERVAIS: Yes.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 758}, {"answer": "I -- I -- oh, I love kids.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "I'll bet you'd be a good dad, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 760}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "Do you feel lucky to have someone like Jane, then?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "There's no secret.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "Without being cheesy about it, what has been the secret to it?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "And that, after 25 years or more, is a pretty amazing achievement --", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 789, "question": "Well, that's -- that's important, isn't it?", "qSentId": 788}, {"answer": "She said I've -- I've got the fast car, here's your disguise and I've got two tickets to Cuba.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "What did she say to you after the Globes this year?", "qSentId": 794}, {"answer": "It is true, but it was meant to be a secret one.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 810, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 809}, {"answer": "I just bump into Steve Carell.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "What's the part you play?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "Yes, you just act like an idiot.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 822, "question": "So you play David Brent?", "qSentId": 821}, {"answer": "Oh yeah.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 829, "question": "When you first saw Steve Carell playing his version, did you feel like I did, ah, what a relief, he can do it?", "qSentId": 828}, {"answer": "Yeah, well, I sent him an email saying I think you did the right thing.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 840, "question": "Did Steve tell you that he was leaving the American version?", "qSentId": 839}, {"answer": "Laurel and Hardy would count for two of them straight away.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 851, "question": "If you could be trapped on a desert island with three other comedians in history, who would they be?", "qSentId": 850}, {"answer": "The funniest man you've ever seen or woman in America.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 856, "question": "Comedian?", "qSentId": 855}, {"answer": "There's four jokes I just realized I can't tell.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 878, "question": "If you had five minutes left to live, what's the joke you'd tell?", "qSentId": 877}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 907, "question": "It is two season and bang?", "qSentId": 906}, {"answer": "A great question.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 916, "question": "Which is a brilliant question, isn't it?", "qSentId": 915}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 924, "question": "Are you mad?", "qSentId": 923}, {"answer": "I knew they were good.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 929, "question": "Did you ever imagine you'd be too busy to be in three of the greatest franchises in movie history?", "qSentId": 928}, {"answer": "ERVAIS: I never thought about I'd ever be offered a movie.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 932, "question": "But did you ever think, when you were a young Ricky Gervais, that you could ever be in that position, to turn movies down like that?", "qSentId": 931}, {"answer": "Probably about seven or eight million.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 941, "question": "How many DVDs have you sold?", "qSentId": 940}, {"answer": "Oh, come on.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 943, "question": "So how rich are you?", "qSentId": 942}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 947, "question": "Are you richer than him?", "qSentId": 946}, {"answer": "Work hard and pay your way.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 967, "question": "What were the values that they instilled in you, do you think?", "qSentId": 966}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 971, "question": "And do you?", "qSentId": 970}, {"answer": "No, I enjoy the hard work.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 974, "question": "Do you get to enjoy the fruits of your hard work, you think?", "qSentId": 973}, {"answer": "My father taught me never to mix grain and grape at a very young age.", "docId": "110120pmt", "aSentId": 993, "question": "What values do you think they instilled in you as a young -- a young George?", "qSentId": 992}]